Guide to the C. Harrison Mann, Jr. papers, 1950-1977
George Mason University Libraries
- C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Collection
  - G.M.U - Broadside newspapers, Clippings. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - G.M.U Finance. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - G.M.U Correspondence. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Gunston Hall - G.M.U. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - G.M.U History. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - G.M.U Law School. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - G.M.U Law School. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - G.M.U Misc. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - G.M.U Misc. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - G.M.U Pamphlets, etc. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - G.M.U Pamphlets, etc. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Law School Reports - Advisory Committee. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Tenure in Universities and Colleges. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Info. for G.M.U's Advisory Board. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Marine Corps Reserve. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Marine Corps Reserve II. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Correspondence 1946 - 7 Military Matters. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Marine Corps Active Duty Orders. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Marine Corps Active Duty Orders. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Mental Health. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mental Health. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Mental Health. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Mental Health. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Mental Health. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Mental Health. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Mental Health. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Mental Health (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly - Mental Hospital 1960 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - UVA. Architecture. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - UVA. 1946 - 48. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - UVA. Washington Chapter 1946 - 47. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - UVA. Washington Chapter 1948 - 49. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Branch - UVA. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Branch - UVA. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - UVA. Branch Correspondence. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - UVA. Branch Correspondence. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - UVA. Branch Correspondence. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Branch (Important) (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Branch Maps and Proposed No. VA Site (Letter). (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Branch Maps and Proposed No. VA Site (Letter). (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - College Building Authority. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Education - Extension (Correspondence and Memos). (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Education - Printed Data. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Education - Extension - Mimeographed Data. (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Education Extension - Printed Data, Clippings, Pamphlets. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Education - General Assembly 1960. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Education - General Assembly 1960. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Community College. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - State Plans. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Private Plans SEAA. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Administration SEAA. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Minutes SEAA Aug 9, 1960. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - S.E.A.A 1960. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - S.E.A.A 1960. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - S.E.A.A 1961. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - S.E.A.A 1961. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - S.E.A.A 1962. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - S.E.A.A 1963. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - S.E.A.A 1964. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - S.E.A.A 1965. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - S.E.A.A 1966. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - S.E.A.A 1967. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - S.E.A.A 1968 - 69. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - S.E.A.A 1968 - 69. (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - S.E.A.A 1970 - 75. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence and Information on Colleges. (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence and Information on Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Information on Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Info. on Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Info. on Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Colleges. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly I: Education, Correspondence, Clippings. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly I: Education, Correspondence, Clippings. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly I: Education, Correspondence, Clippings. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Education. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Education. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Education. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - General Assembly - Colleges 1966 -68. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets on Colleges, States Legislatures. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Gen. Assembly I Schools, Data. (Box 25, Folder 3A)
  - General Assembly I Schools Data. (Box 25, Folder 3B)
  - General Assembly II Schools Data. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Constitutional Amendment. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Schools - 1968. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Re The Board - Schools News Items. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Schools G.A. 1966. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Constitution. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Subcommittee Report on Justices of Peace. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Courts. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Juvenile Court. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Minutes. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Studies. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Va. Conference. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - National Conference on the Judiciary. (Box 25, Folder 16A)
  - National Conference on the Judiciary. (Box 25, Folder 16B)
  - Report: The Court System of VA. (Box 25, Folder 17A)
  - National Conference on the Judiciary. (Box 25, Folder 17B)
  - Reports (Ct. System). (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Court Systems. (Box 26, Folder 2A)
  - National Conference on the Judiciary. (Box 26, Folder 2B)
  - Reports on Court Systems. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Judge. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Justices of Peace. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Courts. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Budget. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly Budget 1960. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly Budget 1962. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Budget 1964. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Budget 1964. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Budget. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Budget. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Bonds. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Budget 1968. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Finances - General Assembly. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Finances. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Self Insurance ( Gen. Assembly 1960). (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - State Corporation Commission. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly (School Banking). (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Regulations for Debt. Pooling or Financial Management Services. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Insurance. (Box 27, Folder 5A)
  - Insurance. (Box 27, Folder 5B)
  - Insurance Rates. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Insurance (General Assembly, 1960). (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Credit Life Insurance (General Assembly, 1960). (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Credit Unions (General Assembly, 1960). (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Insurance. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Interest Rates. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Interest Rates. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Insurance (General Assembly, 1966). (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Insurance (General Assembly, 1966). (Box 27, Folder 14A)
  - Insurance (General Assembly). (Box 27, Folder 14B)
  - Automatic Tax Reduction. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Sales Tax - 1960. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Taxation: Press (General Assembly II). (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Taxation - Correspondence Only. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Sales Tax. (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Real Estate Assessments 1962 - 1964. (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Sales Tax Law - 1966. (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Inheritance Tax. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Taxes 1960. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Land Taxes. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Taxes 1968. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Sales Taxes 1966 (General Assembly). (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly 1966 Sales Tax. (Box 28, Folder 4A)
  - General Assembly 1966 Sales Tax. (Box 28, Folder 4B)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1954. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1954. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1954. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1954. (Box 28, Folder 8A)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1954. (Box 28, Folder 8B)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1956. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1956. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Bills Passes - Killed 1958. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Chemical Test Bill 1958. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Bills Passed (General Assembly 1962). (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Bills Passed 1962. (Box 28, Folder 14A)
  - Bills Passed 1962. (Box 28, Folder 14B)
  - Bills Passed 1964. (Box 28, Folder 15A)
  - Bills Passed 1964. (Box 28, Folder 15B)
  - Index 1954 - 62 (Bills, Joint Resolutions of VA Gen. Assembly). (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Index 1954 - 62 (Bills, Joint Resolutions of VA Gen. Assembly). (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Index 1954 - 62 (Bills, Joint Resolutions of VA Gen. Assembly). (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Moncure Bills #2 letters to Delegates. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Moncure Bills #2 letters to Delegates. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly - 1960 Bills Passed. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly - 1960 Bills Passed. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Kerr - Mills Bill. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Legislation 1962. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Legislation 1962. (Box 29, Folder 10A)
  - Legislation 1962. (Box 29, Folder 10B)
  - Legislation 1964. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Legislation 1965 Objectives. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Bills Passes 1966. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Bills Passes 1966. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Bills Passes 1966. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Bills Passes 1966. (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Legislation 1956. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly Legislation 1957. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Legislation 1958. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Legislation 1958. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Legislation 1958. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Info. on Projected Legislation, 1959 - 1962. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Legislation 1960. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Legislation 1960. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Committee - 1961. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Legislation (County Board) 1962. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Legislation #2 1962. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Legislation 1964. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Legislation Requests. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Legislation. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Legislation 1966 (General Assembly) Public Land Utility. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Legislation 1968. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Legislation 1968. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Legislation 1968. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Legislation Appendix 1968. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Legislation 1970. (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - General Assembly Roll Call Votes 1954. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Votes (General Assembly 1960). (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Votes 1962 (General Assembly) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Votes 1964. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Statement (Mann) Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Members Trucks 1962 Citizens Committee To Protect VA's Highways. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Pro - Truck 1962. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Hearings Trucks - 1962. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - States - Trucks 1962 Oregon - NY Mars commission. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Trucks Citizens Comm. - to Protect Va. Highways. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - VMI Truck Study. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Statistics Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Reciprocity Trucks - 1962. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Fuel Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - License Fees Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Fines Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Editorial Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Legislation Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - History Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Taxes - Comparative Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - 1970's Material on Trucks, Highway Safety. (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Material on Trucks and Highways. (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Material on Trucks. (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Twin - Trailer Trucks. (Box 31, Folder 24A)
  - Twin - Trailer Trucks. (Box 31, Folder 24B)
  - Useful Facts Trucks 1962. (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Trucks, Highway Taxes. (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Trucks (General). (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Reports on Highway cost allocation, Road Test Results. (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Reports on Highway Cost Allocation, Road Test Results. (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Reports on Highway Cost Allocation, Road Test Results. (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Highway Taxes. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Highway Taxes. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Trucks 1962 Clippings. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Trucks 1962 Newspaper Costs. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Misc - Trucks 1962. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Radio Costs Trucks 1962. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Radio Costs Trucks 1962. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Court Cases - Trucks 1962. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Editors Trucks 1962. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Trucks 1962. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - AASHO (Road Test) 1962, for Trucks. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Trucks 1962 Official Correspondence. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - advertisements 1962 (Newspapers, Radio, Trucks). (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Trucks 1962 Correspondence. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Trucks 1962. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - General Assembly Trucks 1966. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Trucks 1968. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - General Assembly - Trucks. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Trucks General. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Twin Trailers. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Weight - Distance. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Trucks - Weight Distance Tax. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Trucks - General. (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Trucks - General. (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Billboards 1959 - 61 Correspondence. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Billboards 1959 - 61 Correspondence. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Billboards 1965 - 67. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Billboards 1965 - 67. (Box 33, Folder 4A)
  - Billboards 1965 - 67.1 (Box 33, Folder 4B)
  - Billboards. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Billboard. (Box 33, Folder 6A)
  - Misc. Billboard. (Box 33, Folder 6B)
  - Billboard and Highways. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Billboard and Highways. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Billboard and Highways. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - A - E Cards From Supports of Billboard Law. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - J- M Cards From Supports of Billboard Law. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Mc - T Cards From Supports of Billboard Law. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - UV - Z Cards From Supports of Billboard Law. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Billboards 1972. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Billboards 1973 (Congress Record). (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Billboards 1973 - 74. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Billboards. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Billboards. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Billboards. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Billboard Correspondence. (Box 34, Folder 6A)
  - Billboard Correspondence. (Box 34, Folder 6B)
  - Billboard Correspondence. (Box 34, Folder 7A)
  - Billboard Correspondence. (Box 34, Folder 7B)
  - Associated Clubs for Roadside Development. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Billboard - Garden Club of Va. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Billboard Issues. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Billboard Speed Material. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Billboards General. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Bridges. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Shirley Highway. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Rt. 66 - Bridge Over Potomac. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Route 66. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Shirley highway - 1961 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Shirley highway - And Mass Transit. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Highway Correspondence - Notes. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Publications. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Highways: News Clippings. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Oregon Highways. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Reports on Highways. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Reports on Highways. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - I - 66 and 3 Sisters Bridge. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - I - 66 Press Club Material. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Portion of Study on I - 66. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Opposition (Clippings and Correspondence). (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Press - Clips - I 66. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Wash and Old Dominion R.R. 1965. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Old Dominion R.R. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Highway Safety. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Highway Safety. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases - (Traffic Safety). (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - A Challenge (Traffic Safety). (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Material on - (Traffic Safety). (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Reports on Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Reports on Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Action on Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Chamber of Commerce - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Commission - 1st Meeting - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Committees - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Communication - React and Help. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Confiscation - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Drinking Drivers - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - General Assembly 1960 Drunk Driving. (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Driver Ed (Traf. Safety). (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Help - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Inspections - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Insurance Institute. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Institute. (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Highway Dept. (Traffic Safety). (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Engineering - Inspection Committee (Traffic Safety). (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - General - Traffic Safety. (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Medical. (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Enforcement. (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Locations. (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Hearings. (Box 36, Folder 27A)
  - Hearings. (Box 36, Folder 27B)
  - J.C's (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Meetings - Traffic Safety. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Minutes - Traffic Safety. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Motor Vehicle Administration (Traff. Safety). (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Names (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clips (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Norway - Sweden (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - School Bus (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Highway Safety Newsletters. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Highway Safety Pamphlets. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Va. Committee highway Safety - Mimeograph Copy. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Sub - Committee (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Reports - (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Study proposal (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Study Proposals (Traffic Safety). (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - State Safety Requirements. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Traffic Safety: 1963 - 65. (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Highway Safety 1966 - 72. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Highway Safety 1973 - 76. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Highway Safety 1973 - 76. (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Motorcycles. (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Plastic Licenses. (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Drunk Driving. (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Traffic Safety Correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Traffic Safety Correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Traffic Safety Correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gen. Assem. 1947 - 56 Alcoholics (Printed Data). (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Gen. Assem. 1947 - 56 Alcoholics (Clippings, Letters). (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Sunday Blue Laws - Arlington Co. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly 1958. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly 1958. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly 1958. (Box 38, Folder 9A)
  - General Assembly 1958. (Box 38, Folder 9B)
  - No. Va. Tour Gen. Assem. 1960. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Letters Gen. Assem. 1960. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Gen. Assem. 1960 Clippings. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Urban Renewal - Gen. Assem. 1960. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Gen. Assembly - Williamsburg. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Gen. Assembly - Va. Advisory Legislative council. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Gen. Assembly - Motion Pictures, 1956. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Safety General Assembly 1960. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly Obscenity 1960. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly 1960 Aging. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly 1960 Divorce. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly 1960 County Board. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly 1960 County Board. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly 1960 General. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly 1960 General. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Sterilization 1962. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Gen. Assembly 1970. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly - Clippings. (Box 39, Folder 12A)
  - General Assembly - Clippings. (Box 39, Folder 12B)
  - Gen. Assembly Procedure. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Gen. Assembly - Public Utilities. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Gen. Assembly - Recreation. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Gen. Assembly - Requests for Support. (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Gen. Assembly - Retirement. (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Gen. Assembly - Churches. (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Gen. Assembly - Gambling. (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Gen. Assembly - Voluntary Sterilization. (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Juvenile - Gen. Assembly. (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Gen. Assembly Libraries. (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Loyalty Oath. (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Gen. Assembly Equalization. (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Gen. Assembly Game. (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Game 1968. (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Gen. Assembly - Old Members. (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - General Assembly - Commendations. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly - Commission on Constitutional Govt. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly - Committees. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly - Conservation. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly - Consumers. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly - Crime. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly - Dogwood. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly - Drafting Division. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly - 1966 Retarded. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly - Voting Rights 1966. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - General Assembly - Civil War Commission. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly - Civil War Commission. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Tour of State Institution by the Legislature. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Arlington Co. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Arlington Co - General Assembly - (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Arlington Co - General Assembly - 1962. (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Reports on Incorporation of Arlington's Finances. (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Reports on Incorporation of Arlington's Finances. (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Arlington Co. (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Milk Commission 1965. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Milk Commission 1965. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Milk Commission I. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Milk Commission VALC. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly - Milk Commission. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Perrow Commission 1962 - 63. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Perrow Commission Correspondence. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Perrow Commission - Clippings. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Perrow Commission - Clippings. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Perrow Commission. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Perrow Commission. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Perrow Commission. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Perrow Commission - Public Education. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Perrow Commission (Committee Reports, Proposed Bills, dealing with Public Education). (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Perrow Commission (Committee Reports, Proposed Bills, dealing with Public Education). (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Material on Perrow Commission. (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Material on Perrow Commission. (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Perrow Commission. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Perrow Commission. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Perrow Commission. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Perrow Commission. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 5A)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 5B)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 8A)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 8B)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Reapportionment. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Special Sessions 1956 Clippings. (Box 43, Folder 3A)
  - Special Sessions 1956 Clippings. (Box 43, Folder 3B)
  - Special Sessions 1956 Proposed legislation. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Special Sessions 1956. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Special Sessions 1956. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Special Sessions 1959 - School Crises. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Special Sessions 1959 - School Crises. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Special Sessions 1963. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Special Sessions 1963. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Special Sessions 1963. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Special Sessions 1964. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Special Sessions 1965. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Constitution (Revision 1969 Special Session. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Special Sessions 1969. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Catholic - Special Sessions 1969. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Gray Commission - Clippings. (Box 44, Folder 5A)
  - Gray Commission - Clippings. (Box 44, Folder 5B)
  - Gray Commission - Clippings. (Box 44, Folder 6A)
  - Gray Commission - Clippings. (Box 44, Folder 6B)
  - Gray Commission - Clippings. (Box 44, Folder 7A)
  - Gray Commission - Clippings. (Box 44, Folder 7B)
  - Gray Commission - Clippings. (Box 44, Folder 8)